== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Penny:)Well, where is he?
(Amy:)Sheldon?
(Leonard:)I'll check his room.
Surprise!
(both scream)
Oh, my God!
(Sheldon:)Just one example
(Sheldon:)of how birthdays
can be terrible.
(Sheldon:)Now, can we please
(Sheldon:)drop this subject
and pick a new one?
Yeah, I suggest
“how thick can a soup get
before it becomes a stew?”
(Sheldon:)You know, the answer,
it may surprise you.
(Amy:)I'm sorry I brought it up.
(Penny:)Yeah, what is the problem?
(Penny:)Is it about getting older?
(Sheldon:)Please, look at this
porcelain skin.
(Sheldon:)I'm like a human sink.
(Amy:)But it's the one day a year
that's just all about you.
(Amy:)One day.
(laughs)
(Leonard:)Right.
(Amy:)Can you please just tell me why?
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)As you know,
I have a twin sister
(Sheldon:)with whom I obviously
share a birthday.